Amirhossein SEFATI

Sasanipour Street, Tehran, Iran | +98 935 4237 134 ahsefati77@gmail.com | www.ahsefati.ir



Professional summary

Motivated "Industrial Simulations" with 3 years of progressive experience in the Internet of Things (IoT) industry. Offering expertise in MATLAB, Programming and Managing, with aptitude in learning new fields. Energetic self-starter and team builder able to navigate high-stress situations and achieve goals on time.

Work history

July 2019 - current

Industrial Robotics Controller

Tinaio co.

Tehran

- I design server and back-end programs. I want to know more about how to simulate robots and industrial devices before creating and testing them in real-world.
- Simulating some parts of IoT devices for smart connecting with Proteus and also some of circuits in Simulink-Matlab.

October 2018 - current

Web Developer and Designer

Tipica co.

Tehran

- Designing, implementing and monitoring web pages and sites for continuous improvement in a fast-paced environment.
- Managing the team at meetings with executives, and discussing about project goals.
- Employing programming capabilities in PHP, MySQL and JavaScript and other libraries as needed.

Skills

Electrical Skills:

- MATLAB programming
- Simulink simulations
- Proteus simulations
- Python programming
- Arduino programming (C++)
- ARM programming (C)
- Altium Designer

Computer Skills:

- Java programming
- JavaScript programming
- Php programming
- MySQL database
- HTML5 and CSS3
- Data structure and Algorithm Design
- MQTT protocol

Education

2020

Bachelor of Electrical Engineering

Amirkabir University of Technology

- Having an "A" GPA
- Working in Innovation and Technology Center (ITC) in Electrical engineering department
- Holding and teaching "IoT platform design" course in ITC
- Participating in several conferences about Industrial problems and how to solve them with low-budget

2020

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Amirkabir University of Technology

- Field of "Software engineering"
- Having an "A" GPA
- Participating in several labs about Software design, Operating systems,
 Computer network, Multi-Thread programming and etc
- Creating a web-app site for projects about developing online services in some courses
- Interested in creating simulator and plotter apps like MATLAB-Simulink

2020

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Amirkabir University of Technology

- Field of "Artificial Intelligence"
- Having an "A" GPA
- Interested to create simulations of human and behavior of him/her.

Tips:

- I study Electrical and Computer engineering in Amirkabir university simultaneously having two separate student IDs for each of them.
- I am so interested in learning new things and in my opinion, I always learn fast!
- I have this ability to work and study all day long.



Amirkabir University of Technology B.Sc. Transcript

First name: **AMIRHOSSEIN** Student No.: 9531702

Last name: **SEFATI** Date Printed: 5 February 2020

Semester Status: Normal

Computer Engineering-Computer Engineering Department:

First Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)

First Semester 2018 -		Semester Status: Normal						
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments
Discrete Mathematics				3101033	3	17.75		
Advanced Programmir	ng			3101043	3	19.25		
Advanced Programmir	ng Lab.			3101051	1	19.25		
Special Topics (Applie	ed Linear Algebra)			3102103	3	14.1		
Taken Units: 10	Passed Units: 10	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	e Units: 0	W	ithdrawn Un	its: 0	Average: 17.26
Total Taken Units: 10	Total Passed Units: 10	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdray	vn Units: 0	Total Average: 17.26

Second Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)

Course Title					Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments
Data Structures and Algo	orithms			3102033	3	15.5		
Computer Architecture				3102073	3	17.95		
Computer Architecture I	Lab.			3102081	1	17.95		
Taken Units: 7	Passed Units: 7	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 0	Average: 16.9
Total Taken Units: 17	Total Passed Units: 17	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdrav	vn Units: 0	Total Average: 17.11

First Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399)

First Semester 2019 -		Semester Status: Norma						
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments
Principles of Database	Design			3102313	3	16.12		
Microprocessor and As	ssembly Language			3103013	3	19.6		
Microprocessor and As	ssembly Language Lab.			3103021	1	19.6		
Operating Systems				3103033	3	16.4		
Operating Systems Lab).			3103041	1	20		
Computer Networks				3103053	3	16.1		
Computer Networks La	ab.			3103061	1	16.1		
Taken Units: 15	Passed Units: 15	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 0	Average: 17.36
Total Taken Units: 32	Total Passed Units: 32	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdray	wn Units: 0	Total Average: 17.23

Second Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399)

Second Semester 2019 -	Semester Status: Normal						
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Theory of Machines and I	Languages			3102093	3		UNRECEIVED
Algorithm Design				3102213	3		UNRECEIVED
Principles of Compiler De	esign			3102323	3		UNRECEIVED
Software Engineering I				3103073	3		UNRECEIVED
Taken Units: 12	Passed Units: 0	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	Units: 0	W	ithdrawn Units	s: 0 Average: 0
Total Taken Units: 44	Total Passed Units: 32	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdrawr	1 Units: 0 Total Average: 17.23

This is an unofficial transcript issued solely for the student information and possible use for provisional admission to the graduate school. The official transcript will be provided upon formal request to: Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs, Amirkabir University of Technology, P.O.Box 15875-4413 Tehran, Iran, registraroffice@aut.ac.ir

Not valid without signature and authorized seal of the registrar, both on the transcript and the envelope.



Amirkabir University of Technology **B.Sc.** Transcript

First name: AMIRHOSSEIN Student No.: 9523076

SEFATI Last name: Date Printed: 5 February 2020

Semester Status: Normal

Semester Status: Normal

Electrical Engineering-Electrical Engineering Department:

First Semester 2016 - 2017 (1395 - 1396)

Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Math. (I)				1011053	3	15.25	
General Physics (I)				1021303	3	15.75	
General Physics (II)				1021353	3	14.5	
Islamic Thought (I)				1051122	2	19.5	
English for the Student	ts of Engineering			1061103	3	17.03	
Computer Programmin	ıg			2302023	3	18.5	
Electricity Lab.				2302511	1	19	
Taken Units: 18	Passed Units: 18	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	e Units: 0	W	thdrawn Un	hits: 0 Average: 16.73
Total Taken Units: 18	Total Passed Units: 18	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdray	wn Units: 0 Total Average: 16.73

Second Semester 2016 - 2017 (1395 - 1396)

Second Semester 2016 -	2017 (1395 - 1396)						Semester Status: Normal
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Math. (II)				1011103	3	17.43	
Differential Equations				1011253	3	16.5	
Numerical Analysis				1011402	2	17.75	
General Physics Lab (I)				1022371	1	20	
Farsi				1051203	3	19	
Islamic Rev. of Iran				1051412	2	19.75	
Probability & Statistics				2302013	3	17.2	
Electric Circuits (I)				2305033	3	19	
Taken Units: 20	Passed Units: 20	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	Units: 0	W	thdrawn Un	its: 0 Average: 18.12
Total Taken Units: 38	Total Passed Units: 38	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdrav	vn Units: 0 Total Average: 17.46

First Semester 2017 - 2018 (1396 - 1397)

First Semester 2017 - 2	Semester Status: Norma						
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Modern Physics				1021253	3	17.5	
Islamic Thought (II)				1051132	2	19	
Electric Circuits Lab				2302061	1	19.5	
Engineering Mathematic	s			2303043	3	16.75	
Electric Circuits (II)				2305063	3	17.8	
Electromagnetics				2305073	3	14.25	
Eletronics (I)				2305093	3	17	
Taken Units: 18	Passed Units: 18	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 0 Average: 17.08
Total Taken Units: 56	Total Passed Units: 56	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	То	tal Withdrav	wn Units: 0 Total Average: 17.34

Second Semester 2017	- 2018 (1396 - 1397)						Semester Status: Normal
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Physical Education (I) *	Physical Fitness			1040211	1	18.5	
the History of Islamic C	Culture & Civilization			1051032	2	19.5	
Eletronics Lab. (I)				2302091	1	19	
Electronics (II)				2305113	3		WITHDRAWN
Electrical Machines (I)				2305153	3	17.2	
Logic Circuits				2305183	3	13.5	
Signals & Systems				2305213	3	14.6	
Technical English				2307002	2	18.5	
Research Methods & Ro	eport Writing			2384132	2	19	
Taken Units: 20	Passed Units: 17	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 3 Average: 16.91
Total Taken Units: 76	Total Passed Units: 73	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	То	tal Withdrav	vn Units: 3 Total Average: 17.24

First Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)

Course Title	Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Physical Education (II) * Hockey	1040161	1	18.5	



Amirkabir University of Technology B.Sc. Transcript

First name: **AMIRHOSSEIN** Student No.: 9523076

Last name: **SEFATI** Date Printed: 5 February 2020

Semester Status: Normal

Electrical Engineering-Electrical Engineering Department:

First Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)

Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments
Practical Mysticism in	Islam			1051322	2	19.5		
Electronics (II)				2305113	3	12		
Linear Control System	S			2305243	3	10.1		
Communication System	ms (I)			2305273	3	17.6		
Taken Units: 12	Passed Units: 12	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	ve Units: 0 Withdrawn Units: 0		its: 0	Average: 14.72	
Total Taken Units: 88	Total Passed Units: 85	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	Ineffective Units: 0 Tot		tal Withdrav	wn Units: 3	Total Average: 16.88

Second Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398)

Second Semester 2018 - 2019 (1397 - 1398) Semester St										
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments		
Quran Interpretation				1051532	2	18.5				
Logic Circuits Lab				2302181	1	20				
Linear Control Systems	s Lab.			2302241	1	19.25				
Digital Control System	ıs			2304003	3	13.75				
Digital Control System	s Lab.			2305241	1	19.12				
Instrumentation				2356123	3	16.64				
Taken Units: 11	Passed Units: 11	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	e Units: 0	W	ithdrawn Un	its: 0	Average: 16.96		
Total Taken Units: 99	Total Passed Units: 96	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdrav	vn Units: 3	Total Average: 16.89		

Summer 2019 (1398) Semester Status: Normal

Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.	Comments
Training				2347562	2	19.25	
Taken Units: 2	Passed Units: 2	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	e Units: 0	Wi	thdrawn Un	its: 0 Average: 19.25
Total Taken Units: 101	Total Passed Units: 98	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	fective Units: 0	To	tal Withdrav	wn Units: 3 Total Average: 16.94

First Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399)

First Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399)								Semester Status: Normal		
Course Title				Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments		
Instrumentation Lab				2305251	1	20				
Industrial Control				2309173	3	17.3				
Modern Control				2356113	3	14.6				
Taken Units: 7	Passed Units: 7	Failed Units: 0	Ineffectiv	Ineffective Units: 0		Withdrawn Units: 0		Average: 16.53		
Total Taken Units: 108	Total Passed Units: 105	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Ineffective Units: 0		Total Withdrawn Units: 3			Total Average: 16.91		

Second Semester 2019 - 2020 (1398 - 1399)

Second Semester 2019 -	Semester Status: Norm	ıal							
Course Title	Course Code	Unit	Sc./Deg.		Comments				
Electrical Machines (I) Lab.				2302151	1			UNRECEIVED	
Indust. Control Lab				2302171	1			UNRECEIVED	İ
Special Topics (Electrical and Electronic Measurement Systems)				2311072	2			UNRECEIVED	İ
Project				2347510	0			IN PROGRESS	
Taken Units: 4	Passed Units: 0	Failed Units: 0	Ineffective	Units: 0	Withdrawn Units: 0		ts: 0	Average: 0	
Total Taken Units: 112	Total Passed Units: 105	Total Failed Units: 0	Total Inef	tal Ineffective Units: 0		Total Withdrawn Units: 3		Total Average: 16.91	

This is an unofficial transcript issued solely for the student information and possible use for provisional admission to the graduate school. The official transcript will be provided upon formal request to: Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs, Amirkabir University of Technology, P.O.Box 15875-4413 Tehran, Iran, registraroffice@aut.ac.ir

Not valid without signature and authorized seal of the registrar, both on the transcript and the envelope.